<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on Chenkai (Nicholas) Wang</title><link>https://nicholas.wang/articles/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on Chenkai (Nicholas) Wang</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:44:18 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nicholas.wang/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Security Mindset: or say "Engineering Engineering"</title><link>https://nicholas.wang/articles/security-mindset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 15:57:36 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://nicholas.wang/articles/security-mindset/</guid><description>*DISCLAIMER: THIS ARTICLE IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE ARTICLE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE ARTICLE.</description></item><item><title>Out with the old, in with the new!</title><link>https://nicholas.wang/articles/helloworld/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://nicholas.wang/articles/helloworld/</guid><description>To whom it may concern,
Hi!
It is been a long time since my last update on my blog. For those who’ve been here before, you may noticed a radical change here. Yes, you are in the right place. Due to the fact that my last generation blog system was built on top of an under-maintained PHP open source CMS platform and hosted with an Arch Linux system which had its package manager database accidentally delete sometime in 2019, I finally decide to discard the whole system and host a new static version of my blog for the sake of simplicity, robustness, availability and reliability.</description></item></channel></rss>